Guide to the Josef Silverstein papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
Silverstein, Josef papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Josef Silverstein papers, [ca. 1950-1990]
4489
Josef Silverstein.
1.2 cubic ft., 1 reel microfilm.
Reports, articles, and clippings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Reports, articles, and clippings relating to Southeast Asia in general, and to ASEAN (Association of Southeast Asian Nations), the Philippines, Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, Vietnam, and Cambodia, with some materials on overseas Chinese, U.S.-China relations, and Cold War foreign policy. Also, election results from Burma, 1960 and 1990.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor, Rutgers University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Reports, articles, and clippings relating to Southeast Asia in general, and to ASEAN (Association of Southeast Asian Nations), the Philippines, Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia, Vietnam, and Cambodia, with some materials on overseas Chinese, U.S.-China relations, and Cold War foreign policy. Also, election results from Burma, 1960 and 1990.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Silverstein, Josef.; ASEAN.
Subjects:
Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975.; Chinese--Asia, Southeastern.; Cold War.; Elections--Burma.
Places:
Philippines--History--1946-1986.; Singapore--History.; Malaysia--History.; Indonesia--History--1950-1966.; Vietnam--History--1945-1975.; Cambodia--History--1953-1975.; China--Foreign relations--1949-1976.; China--Emigration and immigration.; Burma--Politics and government--1948-
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Reports and clippings relating to Southeast Asia in general, ASEAN, the Philippines, Singapore, Malaysia, Indonesia (Box 1)
- Reports and clippings relating to Vietnam and Cambodia, with some materials on overseas Chinese, U.S.-China relations, Cold War foreign policy, and European integration (Box 2)
- Microfilm: Election results, Burma
  - Statement on votes won by elected Hluttaw representatives and percentage (Reel 1)
  - May 27, 1990 election results - constituency, winner, party - Bago Division (Reel 1)
  - Parties running per state and division (Reel 1)
  - May 27, 1990 election results (Reel 1)
    Shan State
    Kachin State
    Rakhine State
    Kayah State
    Chin State
    Kayin State
    Mon State
    Ayeyardwady Division
    Sagaing Division
    Mandalay Division
    Magway
    Yangon Division
    Tanintharyi Division
  - Mss. case file (English) - Constituency, Petitioner, Accused, Decision of Tribunal (Reel 1)
  - Mss. case file (Burmese) (Reel 1)
  - Burmese document (unidentified) (Reel 1)
  - "The Official Returns for General Election (Burma), 1960: Chamber of Nationalities" (English) (typescript) (Reel 1)
  - Mss. other election results - Chamber of Deputies - 1960 - (Reel 1)
    Burma Proper
    Chin Special Division/Kayah State
    Karen State
    Minority voters
    Chin Speicl Division
  - "The Official Election Returns ( 1960 ), Union of Burma Chamber of Deputies" (English) (typescript) (first 6 pp. mss., 7-33 typescript) (Reel 1)
  - Clipping: Official returns for Lower House (Reel 1)
  - Mss. Election Results ( 1960 ), Chamber of Deputies (Reel 1)
  - Notes on election results (English and Burmese) (Reel 1)
- Series I. Correspondence and Research Files
  - ABSDF, Education (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ABSDF, Burma Students (1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - ABSDF, Burma Students (2 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - ABSDF, Burma Students (3 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alagappa, M. (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alagappa, M. (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alamgir, Jalal (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - All Burma Young Monks Association (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alliance for Democratic Solidarity, Union of Burma (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - ALTSEAN (1 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - ALTSEAN (2 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ALTSEAN (3 of 3) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ambler, John (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Amnesty International (1 of 7) (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Amnesty International (2 of 7) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Amnesty International (3 of 7) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Amnesty International (4 of 7) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Amnesty International (5 of 7) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Amnesty International (6 of 7) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Amnesty International (7 of 7) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Arakanese (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Arin Basu, Asian Pacific Network (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Arnott, David (1 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Arnott, David (2 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Arnott, David (3 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Arnott, David (4 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Arnott, David (5 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Arnott, David (6 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Arnott, David (7 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Arnott, David (8 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Arnott, David (9 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Arnott, David (10 of 10) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - ASEAN (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Asia Wall Street Journal (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Asia Watch Human Rights (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Asia Development Bank (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Asia Forum on Human Rights [poster] (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - U Aung (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Aung Htoo (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Aung Gyi (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Aung Gyi (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Aung San Suu Kyi (1 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Aung San Suu Kyi (2 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Aung San Suu Kyi (3 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Aung San Suu Kyi (4 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Aung Thwin (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Australia + Burma (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Australia Fellowship (1 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Australia Fellowship (2 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Australia Fellowship (3 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Australia Fellowship (4 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Australia Fellowship (5 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Australia Fellowship (6 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Australia Fellowship (7 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Australia Fellowship (8 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Australia Project (1 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Australia Project (2 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Australia Project (3 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Australia Project (4 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Australia Project (5 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Australia Project (6 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Australia Project (7 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Australia Project (8 of 8) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Australia Regime Change (1 or 3) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Australia Regime Change (2 or 3) (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Australia Regime Change (3 or 3) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Australian Council for Overseas Aid (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Australian Human Rights Commission (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Aye Kyaw (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Ba, Vivian (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - U Ba Thaung (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Barner, William; SC Morning Post (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Bavmann, V. (1 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bavmann, V. (2 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bavmann, V. (3 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Bavmann, V. (4 of 4) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Becka, Jan (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Billenness, Simon (1 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Billenness, Simon (2 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Billenness, Simon (3 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Billenness, Simon (4 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Billenness, Simon (5 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Borg, Parker (1 or 2) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Borg, Parker (2 or 2) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bradley, David (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Brang, Seng (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Brohm, John (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - B.U.R.M.A. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Burma Communist Part (1 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Burma Communist Part (2 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Burma Communist Part (3 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Burma Communist Part (4 of 4) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Burma Narcotics (1 or 4) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Burma Narcotics (2 or 4) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Burma Narcotics (3 or 4) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Burma Narcotics (4 or 4) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Burmese 1956 Election Data (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Burmese Socialism (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Callahan, Mary (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Canadian Friends of Burma (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Center for Pacific Asia, Stockholm; U.N. to Maung Myint (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Chao-Tzang Yawanghwe (1 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Chao-Tzang Yawanghwe (2 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Chao-Tzang Yawanghwe (3 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Chao-Tzang Yawanghwe (4 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Chao-Tzang Yawanghwe (5 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Chao-Tzang Yawanghwe (6 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Chilston Park Meetings (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Chins, 1993 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Chins, Chin National Park (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Clapp, Priscilla (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Clapp, Priscilla (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Clifford, Robert L. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Collignon, Stefan (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Collignon, Stefan (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Copenhagan Declaration (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Cornell University, Southeas Asia Program (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Council of Foreign Relations, Burma: A Time for Change ( 1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Council of Foreign Relations, Burma: A Time for Change ( 2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Cragg, James, “Jim Leclar” (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Craig, Louisa Benson (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - “Cries from Insein” (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Criminal Trial Procedure in Burma, Thesis Proposal (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - DAB (1of 2) (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - DAB (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Demaine, Current Economic Problems in Burma (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Democracy and Identity (1 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Democracy and Identity (2 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Democracy and Identity (3 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Democracy and Identity (4 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Democracy and Identity (5 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Democracy and Identity (6 of 6) (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Deutz, Andrew (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Diamond, Larry (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Doctors Without Frontiers (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Dorman, Smith (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Dupice, David (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Dunsford, Jack (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Economic Data, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Erikson, Don (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Essays, Drafts on Burma in Various Stages (1 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Essays, Drafts on Burma in Various Stages (2 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Essays, Drafts on Burma in Various Stages (3 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Euro Burma (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - European Parliament (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - European Union (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Evans, Grant; Australia (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Far East and Australia (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Far East and Australia; Reprints (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Ferguson, John (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fink, Christina (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fischer, Holly (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Fisher, Peter (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Forces in Southeast Asian Politics: A Comparative Inquiry (1 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Forces in Southeast Asian Politics: A Comparative Inquiry (2 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Forces in Southeast Asian Politics: A Comparative Inquiry (3 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Forum for Democratic Leaders; Dec. 1994, Korea (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Free Burma Rangers (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - FSP Lecture ( 1 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - FSP Lecture ( 2 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - FSP Lecture ( 3 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Georgetown Immigration (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Georgetown Immigration (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Gholsh, Amitav (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Goshal, Baladas (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Great Britain; Various Papers (1 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Great Britain; Various Papers (2 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Great Britain; Various Papers (3 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Green November (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Grolier Encyclopedia (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Gutman, Pamela (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Guyot, J. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Hanks, L. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Harn Yawnghwe (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Hart, Donn V. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Harvard Friends of Burma (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Herald Tribune (1 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Herald Tribune (2 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Herald Tribune (3 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Herbert, Patricia (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Honour, H., on Pagan (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Htun Aung Gyaw (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Human Rights Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Humphries, Christian (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Ibrahim, Anwar (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - IGC Reports (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Image Asia (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Institute for Asian Democracy (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Institute for Community and Institutional Development (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - International Center for Development Policy (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - International Human Rights Group (1 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - International Human Rights Group (2 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - International Human Rights Group (3 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - International Human Rights Group (4 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - International Human Rights Group (5 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - International Labor Organization (1 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - International Labor Organization (1 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - International Labor Organization (1 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - International Labor Organization (1 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - International Labor Organization (1 of 5) (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - International Monetary Fund (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - International Monetary Fund (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Interparliamentary Group; Resolution on Burma (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Jesuit Refugee Service (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Johnson, Roger (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Journal of Democracy (1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Journal of Democracy (2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Journal of Democracy (3 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Kachins (1 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Kachins (2 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Kachins (3 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Kachins (4 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Kachins (5 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Kachins (6 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Kachins (7 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Kachins (8 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kachins (9 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kachins (10 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Kachins (11 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Kachins (12 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Kahin, George (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Kanbawza, Win; “Blueprint for Burma” (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Karens; Revolution in Burma (1 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Karens (2 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Karens (3 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Karens (4 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Karens (5 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Karens (6 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Karens; SPDC Special order to Karens on 4/10/99 (7 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Karens; SPDC Special order to Karens on 4/10/99 (8 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Karens; Karen Report Dooplaya (9 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Karens (10 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Karens (11 of 11) (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Karenni, Kaya (1 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Karenni, Kaya (2 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Karenni, Kaya (3 of 3) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Kean, Leslie (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Kennedy, J.F. (1 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Kennedy, J.F.; Kennedy Library, Burma Diversity (2 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Kennedy, J.F.; U Nu + U Thant’s Exasperation, April 1954 (3 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Kennedy, J.F.; 1955-1960 (4 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Kennedy, J.F.; 1961-1968 (5 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Kennedy, J.F.; 1966 (6 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Kennedy, J.F.; Post-Kennedy (7 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Kennedy, J.F.; KMT Leggacy: 1988-1990 (8 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Kennedy, J.F.; G.M.T.K. Notes 1955 (9 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Kennedy, J.F., 1971 Notes (10 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Kennedy, J.F. (11 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Kennedy, J.F.; 1958-1961 (12 of 12) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Khin Maung Kyi; Political Economy of Agricultural Modernization in Burma (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Khin Maung Win (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Khim Mo Kyi (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Khim Mo Kyi (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Khin Maung Ohn (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Khin Nyunt Road Map (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Kilgour, David (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kin Oung (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kin Oung (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Ko Kang (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Ko Kang (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Kosimar, Lucy (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Kuomintang; Evidence of U.S. Involvement (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Kuomintang; Evidence of U.S. Involvement (2of 2) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Kyaw Win (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Kyaw Win (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Kyi May Kaung (1 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Kyi May Kaung (2 of 2) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - La Mar, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Laderman, Carole (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Landmine Report 2000 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Lawyer’s Commission for Human Rights (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Lawyer’s Commission for Human Rights (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Lawyer’s Commission for Human Rights (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Law-Yone, Wendy (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Leifer, Michael (1of 2) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Leifer, Michael (2of 2) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Legal Issues (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Letters (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Liang, Chi-Shad (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Lieberman, Victor (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Lintner, Bertil (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Lintner, Bertil (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Lintner, Bertil (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Lowenstein, Alllard K.; Iliarld, Yale, Response to Ohn Gyaw (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Marshall Project (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Maung, Ardeth (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Dr. Maung Maung (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - May, Ronald (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - May May Khin (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - McConnel, Mitch (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - McGovern, Ed; 1990, DAB (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Military Rule and Politics of Stagnation Manuscript, 1997 (1of 8) (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Military Rule and Politics of Stagnation Manuscript, 1997 (2 of 8) (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Military Rule and Politics of Stagnation Manuscript, 1997 (3 of 8) (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Military Rule and Politics of Stagnation Manuscript, 1997 (4 of 8) (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Military Rule and Politics of Stagnation Manuscript, 1997 (5 of 8) (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Military Rule and Politics of Stagnation Manuscript, 1997 (6 of 8) (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Military Rule and Politics of Stagnation Manuscript, 1997 (7 of 8) (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Military Rule and Politics of Stagnation Manuscript, 1997 (8 of 8) (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Min Son Min (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Min Zin (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Mind The Gap: Can the SPDC’s National Convention Bring Democracy in Burma (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Minoru, Kiryu (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Moynihan, D. (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Moynihan, D. (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Moynihan, D. (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Mons (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Mons (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Mons (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Mya Maung (1 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mya Maung (2 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mya Maung (3 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mya Maung (4 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Mya Maung (5 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mya Maung (6 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Mya Maung (7 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mya Maung (8 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mya Maung (9 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Mya Maung (10 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Mya Maung (11 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Mya Maung (12 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mya Maung (13 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Mya Maung (14 of 14) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Mya Maung’s 1997 Book Draft (1 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Mya Maung’s 1997 Book Draft (2 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Mya Maung’s 1997 Book Draft (3 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Mya Maung’s 1997 Book Draft (4 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Mya Maung’s 1997 Book Draft (5 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Mya Maung’s 1997 Book Draft (6 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Mya Maung’s 1997 Book Draft (7 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Mya Maung’s 1997 Book Draft (8 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Mya Than (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Mya Than (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Mya Than: Foreign Trade in Myanmar Draft (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Myanmar Monitor (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Myint Thein; Burma Freedom Fighters (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Myint Zan (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Nagas (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Nai Mg Mg Thaung (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - The Nation, Bangkok (1 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - The Nation, Bangkok (2 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - The Nation, Bangkok (3 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - National Bureau of Asian Research (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - National Council Union of Burma (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Natural Gas, Yadana (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - National Labor Committee (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - National Reconciliation Project (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - National Unity; Publication Draft by Josef Silverstein (1 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - National Unity; Publication Draft by Josef Silverstein (1 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - National Unity; Publication Draft by Josef Silverstein (1 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - National Unity; Publication Draft by Josef Silverstein (1 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - National Unity; Publication Draft by Josef Silverstein (1 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - National Unity; Publication Draft by Josef Silverstein (1 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - NCGUB (1 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - NCGUB (2 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - NCGUB (3 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - NCGUB (4 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - NCGUB (5 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - NCGUB (6 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - NCGUB (7 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - NCGUB (8 of 8) (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - NDF (1 of 7) [photos] (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - NDF (2 of 7) [photos] (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - NDF (3 of 7) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - NDF (4 of 7) [photos] (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - NDF (5 of 7) [photos] (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - NDF (6 of 7) (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - NDF (7 of 7) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - NLD (1 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NLD (2 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - NLD (3 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - NLD; People’s Parliament (4 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - NLD; People’s Parliament (5 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Norwegian Burma Council (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - O’Donahue, Daniel (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Oil Unocal Case (1 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Oil Unocal Case (2 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Oil Unocal Case (3 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Oil Unocal Case (4 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Oil Unocal Case (5 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Ono Toru (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Open Society (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Open Society Institute, Burma Project (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Open Society Institute, Burma Project (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Orwell Project (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Overholt. William (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Pacific Affairs; Article for Review (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Pack, Mary (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Pa-O People (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Palaung Women, Poisoned FLowers (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Patard, Richard (1 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Patard, Richard (2 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Patard, Richard (3 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Patard, Richard (4 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Peck, Grant; AP Bangkok (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - People’s Liberation Front (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - People’s Tribunal (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Penguin News (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Peschoux, Chirstophe (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Pham, William (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Political Satire Cartoons on Burma (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Post, Ronald (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Princeton in Asia (1 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Princeton in Asia (2 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Princeton in Asia (3 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Princeton in Asia (4 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Princeton in Asia (5 of 5) (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Priyambudi, Sulistiyanto [photos] (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Rabin, Keith (1 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Rabin, Keith (2 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Rabin, Keith (3 of 3) (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Radio Free Asia (1 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 51)